Guide to the Harold Jantz collection of early manuscripts, music manuscripts, and autograph albums, 1477-1905 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- List of Bound Manuscripts
  - German (undated, [18th c.?]): Anon.: Citation derer sieben Planeten und anderer Geister durch die magischen Bilder (Astrological), Manuscript-bound, 165
  - German (1851): Copy of Goethe's Faust, Manuscript-softbound, 166
  - Swedish (1747): Johan Goransson: Is Atlinga, Stockholm: Lars Salvius, 1747, Printed book, 167
  - English (1833-1834): Charles G. Bush: Seaman's journal, Manuscript-softbound, 168
  - German (16th c.-19th c.): A Collection of mostly unbound manuscripts from the 16th through 19th c.: Letters, documents, etc., 169
  - English (17th c.): 3 sheets vellum ms. (shelved in Jantz B. Broadside box), 170